Festival Accompanying Chapter
Part One
Miyo
saa, wasuremashou sono mirai ga
Come, let us forget about the future...
Planning
Takeshi Oikawa
Akihiro Kawamura
Akihiro Yuasa
Original Work ・ Original Story/Supervision
Ryukishi07/07th Expansion
"Higurashi no Naku Koro ni"
"Higurashi no Naku Koro ni Kai"
mata chinurarete yuku nante
...ending up stained in blood again.
Series Composition
Toshifumi Kawase
Character Design
Overall Animation Supervisor
Kyuuta Sakai
Art Director
Chikako Shibata
Color Design
Shinji Matsumoto
namanurui kaze toguro wo maitara
If the soft wind coils up...
Camera Director
Masayuki Kawaguchi
Editing
Masahiro Matsumura
Music
Kenji Kawai
Sound Director
Hozumi Gouda
sore ga tabun aizu
...that is probably a sign.
nukedashitette
Break free.
Opening Theme
"Naraku no Hana"
(Flower in Hell)
Vocals
Lyrics
Composition
Arrangement
Eiko Shimamiya
Tomoyuki Nakazawa
Takeshi Ozaki
kanashisugiru unmei kara
From your heart-wrenching fate.
Music Producer
Music Production
Akira Yoshikawa
Frontier Works
anata wa naraku no hana ja nai
You are not a flower in hell.
Producers
Mika Nomura
Hiroyuki Oomori
Takeshi Okamura
sonna basho de sakanaide
Don't blossom in such a place.
Animation Producer
Animation Production
Kouji Iijima
Studio Deen
sakanaide
Don't blossom there.
karametorarete ikanaide
Don't get entangled.
oto mo naku tobikau toki no kakera
Fragments of time flutter about without a sound.
Kai
Hi
ni
ra
ku
Koro
gu
no
shi
Na
Kai
Production
Higurashi no Naku Koro ni Kai Production Committee
Director
Chiaki Kon
（本を閉じる音）
（美代子(みよこ)）前頭葉？
The frontal lobe?
That's right.
（高野(たかの)）そうだ
脳の一部である前頭葉に―
The frontal lobe is a part of the brain.
特定の干渉をする寄生虫が
存在するという論文だ
It's a thesis on the existence of parasites that cause a specific kind of interference in that part.
（美代子）ふうん
There are countless types of parasites living on Earth...
地球上には
無数の寄生生物が存在し―
時には宿主を支配したりすることが
広く知られている
...and it is a well-known fact that sometimes, they take control of their hosts.
にもかかわらず人体に寄生し―
Nevertheless, the existence of beings that leech off human bodies and control their hosts has been stubbornly denied.
その宿主を支配する存在については
かたくなに否定してきた
どうして？
Why?
ハア
人間を支配するということは―
Taking control over a human being...
人間の思い つまりは
思想をも支配するということだ
...means to take over a human's mind. In other words, his ideas.
（美代子）思想を？
（高野）うん
His ideas?
思想が寄生虫によって
生み出されているとした場合―
If certain ideas are created by a parasite...
それはペストとまったく同じ
...then that would be quite the same as the Black Plague.
つまり 思想は
治療不可能な伝染病と同じになる
In other words, those ideas will become similar to an uncureable epidemic.
この考えを延長すると―
If one extends this thinking...
人種弾圧 あるいは
宗教弾圧の大量虐殺を―
...it might lead to the affirmation of genocides caused by racial or religious oppression.
肯定してしまう論調になりかねん
だから脳内寄生虫を語ることは
戦後 タブーになっておるのだ
That is why talk of brain parasitism has become taboo since after the war.
ふうん
だが脳内寄生虫は必ず存在するのだ
However...
...brain parasites most certainly exist.
（美代子）
うん　それをおじいちゃんが
証明してみせるんだよね？
You are going to prove that, right, Grandpa?
うん？
そのつもりで頑張ってはいるがな
That's what I'm working hard for, of course, but...
Only few researchers have had their theories proven in their own lifetimes.
（高野）仮説を生きているうちに
証明できた科学者は―
限られた者だけだ
おじいちゃん
Grandpa...
Don't worry.
大丈夫　私の研究が
正当な評価を受けられたなら―
If my research ever receives legitimate recognition...
その時 この体が
朽ち果ててしまっていても―
...then even if my body has decayed, my existence will be reborn.
私の存在はよみがえる
Reborn?
よみがえるって？　神様みたいに？
Like a God?
（高野）ああ　その時
おじいちゃんは神様になれるんだよ
Yes.
I'll be able to become a God then.
うわあ 神様に？
（高野）ああ
A God!?
Yep.
[Sky House]
（恵理子(えりこ)）ハアハア
Oh no...
（智美）や… やっぱり
鶏小屋しか開かない鍵なんだよ
This key only opens the birdhouse after all!
Let's give up and go back!
もうやめて戻ろうよ
（恵理子）静かに
Be quiet!
（美代子）恵理子 焦らないで
Eriko.
Stay calm.
その鍵で開くんでしょ？
試したんでしょ？
That key can open the door, right?
You tested it, right?
（恵理子）
鍵は合ってんのよ　固いだけ
It's the right key.
It's just rusty.
（恵理子）ハッ！
（美代子）誰か来た！
Someone came!
恵理子 誰か来るから！
Eriko!
Someone's coming!
This key can open the door!
この鍵で開くんだから
あたしは試したんだから
I tried it out!
Once it's open, we can be happy!
開けば幸せになれる
こんな地獄から おさらばできる
We can say goodbye to this hell!
恵理子　誰か来るよ！
Eriko!
Someone's coming!
ハア… うう ぐっ
（サイレン）
（医師）急いで 早く！
That can wait!
（医師）
そっちは後だ！　こっちから中へ！
Take this one in first!
ああ！
（美代子）お父さん！
Daddy!
Daddy...
お父さん　お母さんはどこ？
どこなの!?
Where's Mommy?
Where is she!?
お父さん お父さん！
Daddy.
Daddy!
（美代子の父）
美代子 ハア よく聞きなさい
Miyoko...
Listen well.
お父さんも お母さんも―
Both Mommy and Daddy...
...lost all of our relatives to the war.
戦争で親類をみんな失ってしまった
So...
だから お父さんが死んだら―
If Daddy dies...
...there will be no one to...
お前の世話をしてくれる人は
誰も… いない
...take care of you...
やだ！　やだよ そんなの
No!
Don't say that!
If Daddy dies...
お父さんが… 死んだら―
...seek the aid of Dr. Takano.
高野先生を頼りなさい
高野一二三(ひふみ)先生だよ
Dr...
...Hifumi Takano.
言ってみなさい
Go to him.
高野… 一二三…
Hifumi...
...Takano?
That's right.
そうだ
高野先生は お父さんの恩師なんだ
Dr. Takano is...
...my professor.
I'm sure...
きっとお前をたす…
...he'll help you...
（美代子）お父さん!?
（父親）はっ ううっ
Daddy!?
（看護師）どいて！
Move!
先生 急変です！
Doctor, his condition is declining!
（医師）いかん 早く手術室へ！
（看護師）はい！
This is bad.
Move him to the operating room!
Yes!
（美代子）お父さん お父さん
お父さん お父さん
Daddy...
Daddy...!
Children's Ward
（職員）
ああ じゃあ あなたの面倒を
見てくれそうな人は？
Then, is there anyone you think could look after you?
（美代子）高野一二三
（職員）その人は誰かな？
Hifumi Takano.
Who is that person?
（美代子）お父さんの先生
Daddy's professor...
そういう人じゃなくて親戚とかは？
Not someone like that...
How about relatives?
ああ 参ったなあ
This is troublesome...
（職員）それでは
よろしくお願いいたします
Please take good care of her.
（職員）分かりました
Understood.
（職員）来い
Come.
I'm sorry...
（女の子）ごめんなさい
ごめんなさい ごめんなさい！
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
（職員）
ハア どうしてだ　どうしてお前は
そんなこともできないんだ！
Why is it...
Why is it that you can't even do that!?
Come here.
（職員）おい！
（女の子）ごめんなさい
I'm sorry!
か… 棺おけの刑だ
（女の子）ごめんなさい
T-The coffin penalty...
ああ！
ごめんなさい！
何？　それ
What's that...?
ああ！
ごめんなさい！
知らない
でも まだいいほうだって
I don't know.
But apparently, it's still one of the lighter penalties...
（扉が閉まる音）
（女の子）ごめんなさい
（扉をたたく音）
（女の子）ごめんなさい　いやあ！
ご… ごめんなさい
（職員）いいから食べろ
I-I'm sorry...
Shut up and eat it.
Y-Yes sir.
は… はい
そっちじゃねえ！
（男の子）ああっ
Not that!
（職員）こっちだよ！
This here!
もったいねえだろうが！
（男の子）んん… ぐっ…
Don't let it go to waste!
Come on!
（職員）おら 食えよ　ああ!?
（せき込み）
Eat it!
食うんだよ　まだ残ってんだろ！
（せき込み）
There's still some left!
（恵理子）ねえ 誰か知ってる？
山の向こうにある児童施設のこと
Hey. Does anyone know?
About the orphanage beyond the mountains.
（菊子）あっ 私 聞いたことある
I've heard about it.
そこでは
おやつの時間もあるんだよね
They even have snack times there.
（智美）院長先生が
とっても優しい人で―
The head of that orphanage is a really kind person...
みんなが“お母さん”って
呼んでるんでしょ
...and everyone calls her "Mommy."
（智美）もうやだよ こんな所
I've had enough of this place...
お母さんのいる所に行きたいよお
I want to go to place with a mother.
みんなは もしチャンスがあったら
脱走したい？
Given the chance, would you guys want to escape?
I would run away if we could.
逃げられるもんなら逃げ出したいよ
But...
でも きっと捕まっちゃうよ
...we'll certainly be caught!
外に出ることだってできないよ
鍵が掛かってるし
We can't even go outside.
The doors are locked.
（美代子）うん
どこもみんな鍵が掛かってる
Everything is locked.
１つだけあるよ
（美代子たち）えっ
There is one way.
中庭の鶏小屋の鍵
The key to the birdhouse in the courtyard.
階段裏のドアを閉めてる鍵と
同じなんだよ
That same key opens the door below the stairs.
（智美）それってほんと？
Is that true?
（美代子）
恵理子 まさかその鍵で…
Eriko...
Can we use that key to...
（智美）やめようよ　危険だよ
Let's not.
It's dangerous.
（恵理子）
もちろん１人なら危険だよ
Of course, it's dangerous to go alone.
But...
でも みんなでなら
少しだけ話は変わってくる
...if we're together, it's a different story.
どうして？
How so?
I heard there's been a mass breakout in the past.
昔 集団脱走があったんだって
（美代子）本当？
Really?
（恵理子）
あいつらは内緒にしてるけど―
They're keeping it a secret...
その時 捕まったのは
１人だけだったんだって
...but they apparently managed to catch only one of the escapees.
Do you know why only one person was caught?
（恵理子）どうして 捕まったのが
１人だけで済んだか分かる？
その子たちはね 全員
バラバラの方向に逃げたの
Those kids all fled in separate directions.
（恵理子）どう？　やってみない？
Well?
Wanna try?
（智美）でも ううっ 怖いよお
But...
I'm scared...
（菊子）私も怖いよ
捕まったら きっと殺されちゃう
So am I.
If we're caught, they'll kill us!
Then do you want to stay here forever?
なら いつまでもここにいる気？
（菊子）あっ…
イヤだ イヤだ イヤだ！
No...
No... No!
I know you're scared.
怖いのは分かる
でも 一度しかないチャンスなの
But this is our only chance.
一度だけの勇気でいい
You only need to muster up the courage once.
What about you, Miyoko?
美代子はどう？
あたしと行かない？
Will you go with me?
絶対に逃げきれる？
Are you sure you can get out?
（恵理子）保証なんかないよ
I can't guarantee anything.
But...
でも あんたが一緒に
来てくれるなら―
...if you come with me...
あたしが１人で逃げ出すよりも
確率は高くなる
...I'll have much better chances of escaping than if I go alone.
もちろん あんたにとってもね
どうする？　美代子
Of course, that goes for you as well.
What will it be, Miyoko?
（開錠する音）
（恵理子）開いた！
It's open!
（職員）おい！
（美代子たち）あっ！
Hey!
What are you doing there!?
そこで何してる！
（職員）脱走だあ！
A breakout!
待て 待てえ！
（職員）ハアハア…
Wait.
Wait!
Okay!
よし　決めたとおりに
バラバラの方向に散って！
Now spread out, just like we agreed!
（職員）待て！
（美代子）ハアハアハア
Hold it!
（職員）待てえ！
（美代子）あっ
Hold it!
んんっ
（美代子）あっ イヤー！
No!
（職員）この野郎
You little bitch!
How dare you bite my finger!
よくも俺の指を… 指を指を指を！
My finger! My finger! My finger!
Higurashi no Naku Koro ni
Kai
Thank you, Sir.
（鷹野(たかの)）
ありがとうございます 先生
このご恩は忘れません
I won't forget your kindness.
（小泉(こいずみ)）ハハハッ　カネは
残りの人生の長い若者が持つべきだ
Money should go to young ones who still have a long life ahead of them.
It is of no use to the elderly.
年寄りが持っていてもしょうがない
大切に使いなさい
Put it to good use.
Of course.
（鷹野）もちろんですわ
I am jealous of Takano-kun.
（小泉）高野君がうらやましいよ
良いお孫さんを持たれて
I'm sure he's bragging about his wonderful granddaughter in Heaven.
きっと
あの世で自慢しているだろう
I have not done anything yet for him to be boastful about.
（鷹野）
まだ 自慢できるようなことは
何もしていません
I believe that when I have completed my grandfather's research...
祖父の研究を完成させた時―
初めて私は
祖父に褒めてもらえると思います
...is when my grandfather will first start praising me.
ハア
You've come a long way, Miyo-chan.
三四(みよ)ちゃんは
今日まで よく頑張ってきた
You are polite and respectful, and have received a great amount of people's confidence and support.
礼を尽くし 大勢の人たちの
信用と支持を取りつけた
Yes.
はい
The fact that I am entrusting you with this money...
そのカネを
私が託すということは―
私が君を 高野君の研究の
正式な後継者だと―
...means that I officially recognize you as the successor to Takano-kun's research.
認めたことなんだ
Thank you very much.
ありがとうございます
深く感謝いたします
I deeply appreciate it.
Back then, I couldn't be of any use at all.
あの時 私は結局
何の力にもなれんかった
Which is why this is also my atonement of sorts towards Takano-kun.
だから それは高野君に対する
私の罪滅ぼしでもある
I believe my grandfather was blessed to have such a great friend.
（鷹野）祖父は
良い親友に恵まれたと思います
うん　私の目の黒いうちは―
I won't allow anyone to hinder you in your research.
三四ちゃんの研究に
一切の不自由はさせん
If anything happens, come to me.
何かあったら いつでも頼りなさい
助力は惜しまないからのう
I will give you my full support.
ンフッ
To think that research such as this...
（閣僚）このような研究が
数十年にわたり眠り続けていたとは
...has been hiding in the shadows for decades...
I hear it didn't receive much support from the top of the military.
（閣僚）
この研究は 軍上層部にも―
ほとんど相手にされなかったと
聞いております
Hence, no one found out about it...
（閣僚）故に 誰にも知られず―
そして ＧＨＱの追及も
受けなかったというわけですな
...and the matter was never investigated by the Allied Supreme Commander, is that right?
It is as if Dr. Takano has taken over your body...
（閣僚）
まるで あなたの体を借りて―
高野先生が 研究を完成させようと
しているかのようですなあ
...to try and complete his research.
（鷹野）ンフフッ
本当にそうかもしれませんわね
That might really be true.
I feel a strange kind of connection as well.
私も奇妙な因縁を感じます
（閣僚）
鷹野さん 誤解しないでくださいよ
Takano-san.
Please do not misunderstand.
The purpose of this research is not to obtain a biological weapon...
この研究は 細菌兵器の保有が
目的ではなく―
その危険性について 事前に
十分な対処を行うための研究です
...but to be able to provide plenty of counter-measures for such a threat.
Yes.
（鷹野）はい 承知しております
I am aware of that fact.
Also, the Council has set up a few conditions.
それと理事会は
いくつかの条件を挙げています
１つは
この研究に関する分野で―
One of them would be to concede leadership to a person of exceptional ability from a field related to this research.
優秀な才能を持つ人物に
研究筆頭を委ねることです
Sorry to object...
お言葉を返すようですが―
私以上に この研究に詳しい人物が
存在するとお思いですか？
...but do you really believe that there is anyone more knowledgable than me about this research?
（閣僚）まあまあまあ
そこは鷹野さん 抑えて抑えて
Well, well...
Takano-san.
Please calm down.
Of course, we will take measures to make things easy for you.
もちろん そこはあなたの
やりやすいように手を打ちます
What do you mean?
（鷹野）と申しますと？
I hold authority over this person's selection.
その人物の人選は
私が握っているということですよ
Nobody is stopping you from selecting a total pushover.
鷹野さんが くみしやすい相手を
選べばいいということです
That's what we mean.
Another thing.
（閣僚）もう１つ
鷹野さんの身分ですが―
Regarding your rank.
You will likely gain the position of second-in-command...
たぶん
副隊長の地位になりますから
おそらく三佐ではないかと
...so I suppose you will be appointed Major.
（鷹野）あっ
（閣僚）おお それは すばらしい
Isn't that magnificent!
Major Takano, huh?
鷹野三佐ですか ハハッ
いやいや うらやましいですな
My, I'm so jealous.
（鷹野）ンフッ
（閣僚）アハハッ
Let me introduce you.
（閣僚）ご紹介します
Major Takano.
鷹野三佐です
Major.
三佐 こちらは入江京介(いりえきょうすけ)先生です
This is Dr. Kyousuke Irie.
N-Nice to meet you.
（入江）
ど… どうも　入江と申します
I'm Irie.
ンフフッ
萎縮しなくて結構ですわ
No need to be nervous.
Please have a seat.
どうぞ おかけになって
（入江）あっ はい
Yes, Ma'am.
I've read the documents on the Hinamizawa Syndrome.
雛見沢(ひなみざわ)症候群の資料
読ませていただきました
What did you think?
（鷹野）いかがでした？
その…
非常に驚くことばかりでした
Well...
It was one surprise after the other.
It's a mystery of the world unraveled by none...
いまだ世界の誰も解明していない
神秘という点で―
I can't stop my intellectual excitement!
知的興奮を抑えきれません
I am quite surprised as well.
（鷹野）私こそ驚いています
To think a well-versed expert such as yourself...
入江先生ほどの経験豊富な方が―
医局の片隅に
飼い殺されていたなんて
...was being wasted away in some backwater medical office...
If I am good enough for you...
（入江）私ごときでよろしければ
この話 ぜひお引き受けいたします
...I would very much like to accept this offer.
Thank you.
ありがとうございます
It'll be a pleasure to work with you.
よろしくお願いいたしますわ
入江所長
Director Irie.
T-The pleasure is all mine.
（入江）こ… こちらこそ
Let me introduce you, Takano-san.
（閣僚）鷹野さん紹介します
富竹(とみたけ)君と小此木(おこのぎ)君です
Tomitake-kun and Okonogi-kun.
Nice to meet you.
（富竹）
はじめまして　富竹と申します
My name is Tomitake.
I have been appointed Inspecting Officer for this project.
この度のプロジェクトの
監査役を仰せつかりました
I am Okonogi.
（小此木）小此木と申します
He belongs to a special warfare unit.
（富竹）彼は不正規戦部隊の１つ
山狗(やまいぬ)の隊長です
The Commander of the Yamainu.
They will be stationed in Hinamizawa, and provide the Major direct support.
雛見沢に常駐し
三佐を直接サポートします
Could I think of you as bodyguards?
ボディーガードみたいなものと
思っていいのかしら？
We are at your beck and call.
三佐の直接の手足となりますので
どうか こき使ってやってください
So please make good use of us.
ンフッ
M-Mommy...
お… お母さん
Find her!?
（職員）いたか!?
（美代子）ハッ
She's not here.
（職員）
こっちにはいない　そっちを捜せ！
Look over there!
Stupid God...
神様のバカ
Why...
どうして私が こんな目に
遭わなくちゃならないの？
...do I have to go through this?
What did I ever do?
私が何をしたの？
Life consists of both good times and bad times...
“人生は いい事と悪い事の
２つがあって―”
Neither will last forever...
“どっちも長続きしない”って
お父さんが言ってた
That's what you told me, Daddy.
Then this won't last forever either, will it!?
だったら
これも長続きしないんだよね！
Put a stop to my misery.
これで私の不幸を終わりにして
And bring me happiness in return for all that I've suffered!
今日までの不幸に見合う
幸福に導いて！
If you can't even do that...
それもできないっていうなら
こんな人生 要らない！
...then I don't want this life!
Kill me!
私を殺して
その雷で私を殺してよ！
Kill me with that thunderbolt!
Kill me!
殺せ
Miyoko Tanashi is right here!
田無(たなし)美代子は ここにいる
Just like you took away my mother and father...
私のお父さんとお母さんを
奪ったように―
...take my life away as well!
私の命も ここから奪え！
Cast
Miyo Takano
Miyoko Tanashi
Kyousuke Irie
Jirou Tomitake
Okonogi
Hifumi Takano
Miyoko's Father
Miki Itou
Fuyuka Ooura
Toshihiko Seki
Tohru Ookawa
Jurota Kosugi
Kazumi Tanaka
Yoshihisa Kawahara
anata no nakigara ni tsuchi wo kakeru
I cover your corpse with soil...
Cast
Eriko
Tomomi
Kikuko
Minister
Staff Officer
Fumie Mizusawa
Kana Hanazawa
Erika
Yoku Shioya
Atsushi Imaruoka
Cast
Cabinet Members
Doctor
Nurse
Orphanage Staff
Child
Bus Driver
Hiroomi Sugino
Tsutomu Densaka
Daisuke Sasaki
Hiroki Yasumoto
Yukiko Matsuyama
Daisuke Matsuoka
Katsuhiro Oota
Risa Mizuno
Gen Nakano
sore ga kinjirareteita toshitemo
...even though that may have been forbidden.
junsui na manazashi no kairaku ni wa
There was a temptation you could not hide...
kakushikirenai yuuwaku ga atta
...in your pure, blissful eyes.
doushite tsumi ga aru no darou
Why does sin exist?
Ending Theme
"Taishou a"
(Target a)
Vocals
Lyrics
Composition/
Arrangement
doushite batsu ga aru no darou
Why does punishment exist?
hone no saki wa amari ni mo shiroku
That blindingly white tip of the bone...
mugen ni tsuzuku yami wo sasotta
...invited the infinite darkness.
Scenario
Toshifumi Kawase
Storyboards
Episode Direction
Sanjin Tomo
Hideki Takayama
nani mo kamo ga azayaka ni miete
I can see everything clearly now.
Animation Supervisor
Animation Supervision Assistance
Norikazu Abe
Shouhei Ohara
Chigai Okado
Hirofumi Morimoto
Kyoko Kotani
Kyoko Kametani
sugu ni kieteshimau
It will soon vanish.
Animation Production
Studio Deen
Production
Higurashi no Naku Koro ni Kai Production Committee
© 2007 Ryukishi07/Hinamizawa Three Great Houses
A dream...?
夢か
（戸をたたく音）
Major.
（隊員）三佐 時間です
It's time.
あっ ありがとう
Thanks.
Any developments?
（鷹野）どう？　何か動きは
（隊員）いえ 何も
No, nothing.
We were contacted by the Gifu team earlier...
（隊員）先ほど 岐阜から
定期連絡がありましたが―
“問題なし”とのことです
...but they weren't experiencing any problems.
I see...
そう
Before long, those abominable memories...
もうすぐ
あの忌まわしい記憶も―
大事な歴史の…
...will become another chapter in my and Grandpa's valuable history.
私とおじいちゃんの歴史の
一部になる
ンフフッ ハハハッ
（梨花(りか)）前回 話題になった
“あうあうう”のことですが
About the "Auauu~" thing we talked about last time...
（羽入(はにゅう)）あまり触れられたくない
問題なのです
I'd rather not touch on that subject anymore...
（梨花）昔 お父さんが
大事にしていたビデオで―
I remember hearing it before in one of my father's treasured videos, a long time ago.
見たことがあるのを
思い出したのです
（羽入）おっ 一体
どんなビデオを見たのですか？
What kind of video was it?
（梨花）
金髪のお姉さんとお兄さんが―
It showed a blond man and woman engaged in professional wrestling inside a car.
車の中で プロレスしている
ビデオだったのです
（梨花）次回　祭囃し編 其の弐
「蠢き」
Next time, the Festival Accompanying Chapter, Part Two.
"Writhing."
（羽入）梨花…
Rika...
Higurashi no Naku Koro ni Kai
Next time
Festival Accompanying Chapter
Part Two
Writhing